{
    "id": "aa98109f0ebd43d797ff2fe2b62ef39c",
    "title": "Idiomatic Expressions Essay",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "His jokes fell ………………………….",
            "description": "If something falls flat it fails to produce the intended result.",
            "answers": [
                "apart",
                "flat",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When his friend was in trouble, he took up the …………………………… on his behalf.",
            "description": "To take up the cudgels is to defend or support somebody.",
            "answers": [
                "weapons",
                "cudgels",
                "armor"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "By endorsing that forged document, he cut his own ……………………….",
            "description": "To cut your own throat is to behave in a way that will cause harm to you.",
            "answers": [
                "head",
                "neck",
                "throat"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Once she entered the show business she seemed to carry all ………………………. her.",
            "description": "To carry all before one is to be completely successful.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "before",
                "in front of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is always bad manners to …………………………… over your opponent.",
            "description": "To crow over is to exult loudly.",
            "answers": [
                "thump",
                "crow",
                "hoot"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Her beauty took my ……………………………. away.",
            "description": "When something takes your breath away you are very much surprised by it.",
            "answers": [
                "heart",
                "mind",
                "breath"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Parental property is the ………………………………. of contention between the brothers.",
            "description": "The bone of contention is the cause of dispute.",
            "answers": [
                "bone",
                "skeleton",
                "ghost"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "When I met him at the party, he cut me ……………………………",
            "description": "To cut someone dead is to insult them by ignoring them deliberately.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "dead"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no harm in using social media, but you must draw the ………………………….. somewhere.",
            "description": "To draw the line is to fix the limits.",
            "answers": [
                "mark",
                "line",
                "circle"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My wife and I do not always …………………………….",
            "description": "To see eye to eye is to agree with.",
            "answers": [
                "hold hand to hand",
                "hear ear to ear",
                "see eye to eye"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He lost the game but put a brave ……………………………… on it.",
            "description": "To put a brave face on something is to accept an unpleasant experience courageously.",
            "answers": [
                "heart",
                "face",
                "smile"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a far …………………………… from his idealistic brother.",
            "description": "To be a far cry is to be very different.",
            "answers": [
                "distant",
                "cry",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}